Welcome to policy plus. Today in our
video we are going to discuss best
health insurance plan for senior citizen
2026.
Before continue this video I request all
if you want health insurance please call
9349036
in WhatsApp.
In this video we are comparing IC eleu
3.0 0 black variant. This is cover
insulin patient also and manipal signal
prime senior elite. This plan also cover
insulin patient.
Enry age
provide coverage up to 110 age. Tata
Medicare you can take any age. Nimuba
also you can take up to 99 age. Manipal
you can take up to 75 age.
Available summer shoot range ICAC
provide coverage from five lakhs to
unlimited. Neaba provide only unlimited
coverage. Tata Medicare select provide
five lakhs to three core coverage.
Manipal train senior relate provide
coverage up to 50 lakhs.
Room rent limit.
ICC eleate provide single private AC
room. If you take 10 lakh policy, you
have the option to take any room.
Neopa provide any room. Tata Medicare
select single AC room. Manipal provide
single AC room and option to increase
any room.
Before continue this video, I request to
all if you not subscribe this channel,
please subscribe to this channel and uh
click this bell button for future
update.
Pre and post hospitalations. ICC provide
up to 180 days. Neub also provide up to
180 days. Tata Medicare select provide
coverage up to 90 days. Manipol also 90
days.
No client bonus. ICC provide default 20%
unlimited bonus also available. Neaba
there is no requirement of bonus because
this policy provide unlimited coverage.
Tata Medicare select provide every year
100% and maximum up to 500%age. Manipal
every year 10%age and maximum up to
100%.
Organ donor expenses. All plans provide
coverage up to summer shoot.
Restore benefit. All plans provide
unlimited restore and newa there is no
restore because already policy provide
unlimited coverage.
pre-existing waiting period ICC 36-month
waiting period also available to day one
coverage for diabetic hypertension ama
and cholesterol by using jump start
rider
same 36 month waiting period and 145
coverage from day one cover rider
available
Tata Medicare also 36 month and option
to reduce waiting period day Phone
coverage available for pressure, sugar,
cholesterol.
Manipal 36 month waiting period and uh
reduction to pre-existing disase waiting
period to 90 days available
specific surgery like pine stone
gallbladder stone ent cat piles ulcer
hernia vicosis waiting period all plans
2 years waiting period and ICC also
available reduce the waiting period to 1
also raider available to reduce the
waiting per one year
biotic surgery.
This coverage available in ICC elevate
cat surgery. All plans provide coverage
up to summer shoot. There is no
restriction.
Health checkup benefit. All plans
provide health checkup benefit as a
rider. Some plan provide amount wise.
Some plan provides specific test
ambulance coverage. All plans provide
coverage up to summer shoot. There is no
conditions. That means you can claim
actual amount
air ambulance coverage.
ICC provide coverage up to summer by
optional. Optional means rider. NAB
provide coverage up to five lakh.
Manipal provide coverage up to 10 lakh.
Tata Medicare Health also provide
coverage.
Oil treatment all plans provide coverage
up to summer
co-ayment if entry age is 60 and above.
All plans provide coverage up to summer
without any co-ayment.
Even Manipal also co-ayment is 20% but
option to rate is zero.
Coverage for modern treatment all plants
provide coverage up to summer shoot.
Coverage for non-medical items like
gloves, mask, sanitizers. Coverage
available as a rider in all plants.
hospitalation that means patient health
is not good to take him to hospital or
hospital not have bed in this condition
you can take treatment at home this
coverage available in all plans
home care treatment
this benefit available in ICC elevate
Nursing at home rider will pay per day
2,000 and maximum up to 10 days.
Hospital cash benefit ICC elevated
convince benefit if you stayed 10 days
hospitalish means possible to claim up
to 20,000 and any child admission in
hospital means cash benefit available.
Neopa also per day 4,000 hospital cash
benefit available as a rider. Tata
Medicare select if you choose sharing
room per day 1,200 or or,500 possible to
claim money not provide hospital cash
benefit
extra benefit
IC provide infra care means any amount
possible to claim inflation product also
available common site visit that means
travel expenses possible Possible to
claim if any family member admission in
other city means possible to claim
travel expenses. Durable medical
equipment coverage available as a rider.
Personal accidental also available as a
rider and critical illness benefit rider
also available and outperson coverage
also available as a rider. Worldwide
cover also available as a rider. NRI
advantage that means
If N taken this policy 25% premium
discount available
NEAP reissue 3.0 Zero cash back that is
premium discount 5% every year
guaranteed one uh claim priority service
available option to reduce the premium
tire network provide premium discount
lock the clock that means your age is
locked up to claims
that also provide 16% premium discount
well consult that is outperson covered
also available as a rider borderless
worldwide cover also available as a
rider.
Tata Medicare select valuable service
provider
that benefit provide discount and
optional to reduce the premium infinite
advantage. Same as ICC infinite care and
early access 3 years policy possible to
claim in 1 year pocket server that is
outperson cover and empower hair that is
checkup for uh woman empower woman
related wellness program and mental
well-being also related to mental
well-being program and cancer benefit
lumpsum payment for cancer direction
external cover also available as a
rider.
Manipal provide discount from network
provider also available and premium
waiver benefit if a proposer died in
external or faced any critical illness.
Premium comparison age 70 and 66
ICC Elliot premium five lakh summer
56,000 and if you choose day one
coverage premium 66,000
nawa unlimited coverage premium 1 lakh
80,000 day one coverage also available
and the premium extra loading based on
health issue
manipul
premium 5 lakhs coverage 66,000
If you choose day 90 coverage 75,000
premium Tata Medicare select Pakers
premium 65,000 day one coverage means
96,000.
Please share suggestion and feedback in
comments. If you like this video please
click in the like button and subscribe
this channel. Share to your friends. For
health concerns please call 934936.
See you next video. Thank you.